Guide to the Brooks McNamara Papers MSS.162
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Subject Files
  - [Copeau, Jacques]: Photocopy., undated (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - [Correspondence (misc.)], undated (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Dance I: Clippings, articles, student papers and bibliographies., undated (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Dance II: Clippings, articles, course materials, student papers and bibliographies., undated (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Dance IV: Articles, programs, research papers., undated (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Dance V: Clippings, programs, fliers, postcards., undated (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Dance VI: Two volumes of "Dance: A Social Study," a multicultural resource., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233752
  - Ballet: Clippings, exhibition brochure., undated (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Dancers and Singers: Clippings, articles., undated (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Davis, Owen: BM article and related research., undated (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Dime Museums I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, pamphlets, correspondence, BM notes on index cards., undated (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Dime Museums II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, fliers, student papers; pamphlet "Some Peculiar Wonders: Part I" (1896)., undated (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Dime Museums III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, pamphlets., undated (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Dime Museums IV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, pamphlets, museum guides., undated (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Dime Museums V: Multiple copies of BM article, "A Congress of Wonders.", 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Dioramas, Etc.: Pamphlets, articles, medallion from a museum in Krakow., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Disney I: Clippings, articles, correspondence; employee newsletter and manual., undated (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Disney II: Articles, photocopies; Disney film rental catalog 1982-3, undated (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Disney III: Clippings, postcards, pamphlets., undated (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Documentary Performance I: Articles, student paper., undated (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Documentary Performance II: Articles, photocopies, student papers, bibliography., undated (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Documentary Performance III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, fliers, course material; BM notes., undated (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Drag I: Course materials, bibliographies, articles., undated (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Drag II: Manuscript by Steven Watson., undated (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Drag III: Clippings, articles, programs, fliers, photographs, student work., undated (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Drag IV: Articles, interviews, student work; book proposal by Laurence Senelick., undated (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - [Edinburgh Military Tattoo]: Pamphlets., undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233760
  - [Edison Filmography], 1989 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Eisenstein: Paper on Eisenstein., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Environmental: Articles, notes, course materials, student work., undated (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Environmental Performance I: Clippings, articles, pamphlets, programs., undated (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Environmental Performance II: Articles, student work., undated (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Environmental Performance III: Articles, photocopies., undated (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Environmental Performance [Misc.]: Articles, photocopies., undated (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Environmental Performance [Misc. 2]: Articles, photocopies, student paper., undated (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Environmental Theatre: Articles, photocopies, student work, course material., undated (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Environments I: Student papers., undated (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Environments II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, pamphlets, photographs., undated (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Environments III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, pamphlets, correspondence, student work., undated (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Environments IV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs., undated (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Ethnic Performance I: Clippings, articles, fliers, programs, student work and bibliographies., undated (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Ethnic Performance II: Student work., undated (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Ethnic Performance III: Clippings, articles, student work, programs, fliers, course syllabi., undated (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - [Ethnic Performance: Conference on the History of Ethnic Performance], undated (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Fairs, 18th C.: Clippings, articles, photocopies., undated (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Fairs, 18th C. "Old Wild's", undated (Box 8, Folder 146A)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233778
  - Fairs I: Clippings, articles, brochures, correspondence., undated (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Fairs II: Clippings, articles, pamphlets, brochures., undated (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Fairs and Expositions III: Clippings, articles, postcards, photocopies, student work., undated (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Fairs IV: Clippings, articles, postcards, photocopies, student work., undated (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Fairs and Expos V: Clippings, articles, postcards, photocopies, student work., undated (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Fairs (Local) VI: Clippings, postcards, photocopies, student work; song book "A Day at the Fair.", undated (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Fairs and Expos VII [Misc.]: Photocopies., undated (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Federal Theater Project I, undated (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Federal Theater Project IIA, undated (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Federal Theater Project IIB, undated (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Festivals: Clippings, articles, programs, photocopies, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 157)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233786
  - Festivals I: Clippings, articles, programs, photocopies, notes, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Festivals II: Student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - Festivals III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - Festivals IV: Clippings, programs, fliers, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - Festivals V: Clippings, articles, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Festivals VI: Programs, notes., undated (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Festivals VII: Clippings, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Festivals VIII: Programs, BM paper drafts., undated (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Festivals IX: Clippings, articles, correspondence, programs, photocopies, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Festivals X: Program, March 1976 National Geographic, student papers., undated (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Festivals XI: Clippings, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Festivals XII: Student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Festivals XIII: Articles, student paper., undated (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Festivals XIV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence., undated (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Festivals XV [Misc.]: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, course materials, student work., undated (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Early Film I: Clippings, articles, photocopies; précis for BM talk on early film era live entertainments., undated (Box 10, Folder 173)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233794
  - Early Film II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, bibliographies, student work., undated (Box 10, Folder 174)
  - Early Film III: Clippings, articles, photocopies; BM paper, "Scene Design and the Early Film.", undated (Box 10, Folder 175)
  - Early Film IV: Student work., undated (Box 10, Folder 176)
  - Early Film V: Clippings, photocopies, program, correspondence, bibliographies., undated (Box 10, Folder 177)
  - Early Film VI: Clippings, photocopies, programs, student papers and bibliographies; exhibition catalog, "American Pastimes," at Brockton Art Center (1977)., undated (Box 10, Folder 178)
  - Early Film VII: Clippings, photocopies, programs, student work, photographs., undated (Box 10, Folder 179)
  - Film VIII: Clippings, photocopies, programs, course materials, student papers., undated (Box 10, Folder 180)
  - Film IX: Clippings, photocopies, programs, brochures, student papers., undated (Box 10, Folder 181)
  - Film X: Clippings, pamphlets, fliers, correspondence, catalogs; 10th Anniversary Issue of Filmfax, 1996., undated (Box 10, Folder 182)
  - Film XI: Draft of student dissertation on DeMille (1983)., undated (Box 10, Folder 183)
  - Film XII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, bibliographies, course materials., undated (Box 10, Folder 184)
  - Film XIII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, correspondence, catalog, bibliographies, course syllabi, student papers., undated (Box 10, Folder 185)
  - [Film: Misc.] Photocopies, bibliographies., undated (Box 10, Folder 186)
  - Fireworks: Clipping; exhibition catalog "Fetes, Fireworks and other Festivities," the Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1971; transcription from Pennsylvania Gazette 12/8/1768 describing fireworks display., undated (Box 11, Folder 187)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233802
  - Folk Art: Clippings, student work; exhibition catalog, "Sacred Images in Secular Art," Whitney Museum of American Art, 1986; materials on Natya Shodh Sansthan., undated (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - Folk and Festival Class Meetings I: Course materials., undated (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Folk and Festival Class Meetings II: Clipping, photocopies., undated (Box 11, Folder 190)
  - Folk Performance I: Student journal about Appalachian culture; article on O-kee-pa ceremony (American Heritage, 1967); student work., undated (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - Folk Performance II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, student papers., undated (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - Folk Performance III [A]: Clippings, articles, photocopies, postcards, student work, bibliography., undated (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - Folk Performance III [B]: Articles, photocopies, postcards, programs, student work., undated (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - Folk Performance III [C]: Clippings, photocopies, programs, student work, BM notes., undated (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Folk Performance III [D]: Articles, photocopies, programs, student work; correspondence re: development of folklore curriculum at NYU (1985); catalog from 1976 Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife; catalog of folklore dissertations (1979)., undated (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - Folk Plays: Clippings, articles, photocopies, bibliographies, student papers; issue of journal Sangeet Natak (1971)., undated (Box 11, Folder 197)
  - Irish Folk Drama: Photocopies., undated (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - Folk Theatre: Photocopies, program, bibliographies, student work., undated (Box 11, Folder 199)
  - Folk Theatre: Asian and African: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs; February 1979 issue of Theatre News on "Asian Theatre"; Fall 1976 issue of Yale/Theatre on "African Theatre"., undated (Box 11, Folder 200)
  - Folk Theatre: New York: Review of book on Chicano and Puerto Rican drama., undated (Box 11, Folder 201)
  - Folk and Pop Lit: Intro: Photocopies, course materials, student work; photocopy of part of "A Typescript Ethnic Joke Anthology"; program for a 1977 "Conference on the History of American Popular Entertainment"., undated (Box 11, Folder 202)
  - Folk [Misc.]: Clippings, photocopies, conference programs; program for "Conference on the Folk Culture of the Bronx"; brochure, "The Fiesta Islands: Festivals of the Philippines"; program for the 1980, "Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife"., undated (Box 11, Folder 203)
  - Freaks and "10 in 1": Clippings, photocopies, correspondence, student work; BM notes; pamphlet "Some Peculiar Wonders: Part II" (1896); 1972 and 1973 issues of "Circus Bannerline"., undated (Box 11, Folder 204)
  - Freaks and "10 in 1": Circus World Museum: Correspondence, photocopies, clippings, photographs., undated (Box 11, Folder 205)
  - Freaks: Clippings, articles, student work on midgets; 1996 calendar from the Mutter Museum., undated (Box 12, Folder 206)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233810
  - Freaks: Mutter Museum calendar., 1996 (Box 35, Folder 674)
  - [Glen Echo Park], undated (Box 12, Folder 207)
  - Grand Guignol: Articles, photocopies, notes., undated (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - Guerrilla Theatre: Photocopy., undated (Box 12, Folder 209)
  - Gypsies: Clippings, correspondence., 1994 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Hoboes, Gypsies, Underworld: Clippings, articles, fliers, correspondence., undated (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Hogarth: Student paper (1966). (Box 12, Folder 212)
  - Horror: Funeral Party journal (1995). (Box 12, Folder 213)
  - Huberts: Article, notes, correspondence., undated (Box 12, Folder 214)
  - [Houdini, Harry: film proposal], undated (Box 12, Folder 215)
  - Ice Shows: Clipping., undated (Box 12, Folder 216)
  - Indians: Correspondence, notes, photocopy., undated (Box 12, Folder 217)
  - Irish Wake Amusements: Photocopy. LETTER THAT DOESN'T BELONG! (move to General Correspondence in box 5???), undated (Box 12, Folder 218)
  - Jewish: Photocopies, student paper with photographs; "Itinerary and Field Guide, Purim - Brooklyn, March 9, 1982" for Barbara Kirshenblatt-Gimblett's Jewish Folk Performance course., undated (Box 12, Folder 219)
  - Juggling: Correspondence., undated (Box 12, Folder 220)
  - [Kirby Slides]: Correspondence regarding Michael Kirby's slide collection., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 221)
  - [Laurentz, Paul]: Photocopies., undated (Box 12, Folder 222)
  - Lecturing: Clippings, photocopies, course syllabi, student work, bibliographies., undated (Box 12, Folder 223)
  - Lecturing: Student paper on Harlem Street Corner Orators., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 224)
  - Lecturing II: Clippings, photocopies, programs, unpublished manuscripts, bibliographies, student work; BM notes., undated (Box 12, Folder 225)
  - Magic I: Clippings, photocopies, programs, fliers, student work; issues of Montandon Magic "Collectors Bulletin" (1959-1964)., undated (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - Magic II: Clippings, photocopies, programs, fliers, student work., undated (Box 12, Folder 227)
  - Magic Papers III: Photocopies, student work., undated (Box 12, Folder 228)
  - Magic IV: Clippings, programs, student work., undated (Box 13, Folder 229)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233828
  - Magic V: Clippings, photocopies, programs, correspondence., undated (Box 13, Folder 230)
  - Magic VI: Clippings, souvenir programs, fliers, magazines, photocopies., undated (Box 13, Folder 231)
  - Magic VII: Clippings, programs, photocopies, magazines, correspondence., undated (Box 13, Folder 232)
  - Magic Lantern: Articles, correspondence, photocopies, BM notes., undated (Box 13, Folder 233)
  - Masques I: Articles, photocopies, program., undated (Box 13, Folder 234)
  - Masques, Court Ents., Disguisings II: Articles, photographs re: Inigo Jones., undated (Box 13, Folder 235)
  - Masque Papers III: Student papers., undated (Box 13, Folder 236)
  - Medicine Show I: Photocopies, correspondence, unpublished manuscript., undated (Box 13, Folder 237)
  - Medicine Show II: Clippings, photocopies, correspondence, newsletters., undated (Box 13, Folder 238)
  - Medicine Show IV: Clippings, photocopies, programs., undated (Box 13, Folder 239)
  - Medicine Show V: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence; Proceedings from the Second National Congress on Medical Quackery, 1963., undated (Box 13, Folder 240)
  - Medicine Show VI: Draft., undated (Box 13, Folder 241)
  - Medicine Show IX: Clippings, photocopies; 1989 issue of Banjo Newsletter., undated (Box 13, Folder 242)
  - Medicine Show X: Photocopies, correspondence., undated (Box 13, Folder 243)
  - Medicine Show XI: Photocopies, correspondence; 1973 issue of Emory College's School of Medicine publication., undated (Box 13, Folder 244)
  - Medicine Show XII: Clippings, photocopies, notes., undated (Box 13, Folder 245)
  - Medicine Show XIII: Clippings, photocopies, notes, draft, correspondence., undated (Box 14, Folder 246)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233836
  - Medicine Show XIV: Photocopies, notes, draft, correspondence., undated (Box 14, Folder 247)
  - Medicine Show XV: Clippings, photocopies, correspondence, notes; catalog for "The American Medicine Show" exhibition, Yale University School of Medicine, 1983-84., undated (Box 14, Folder 248)
  - Medicine Show XVI: Photocopies, interviews, photographs, BM notes; 1969 issue of The Palimpsest "Devils, Drugs, and Doctors", published by the State Historical Society of Iowa., undated (Box 14, Folder 249)
  - Medicine Show XVII: Clippings, photocopies, articles, BM articles, notes, correspondence; 1983 alumni bulletin of the Yale School of Medicine; fall 1983 NYU Performance Studies Department Newsletter., undated (Box 14, Folder 250)
  - Medicine Show XVIII: Clippings, photocopies, articles, correspondence., undated (Box 14, Folder 251)
  - Medicine Show XIX: Photocopies., undated (Box 14, Folder 252)
  - Medicine Show XX: Clippings, photocopies, fliers, paper drafts., undated (Box 14, Folder 253)
  - Medicine Show XXI: Drafts, catalog for The Vitonka Medicine Show., undated (Box 14, Folder 254)
  - Medicine Show XXII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence, drafts., undated (Box 14, Folder 255)
  - Medicine Show Film: correspondence., undated (Box 14, Folder 256)
  - Medicine Show: Photocopies, small booklet in Japanese., undated (Box 14, Folder 257)
  - Medicine Show [package sent from Tommy Scott's Old Time Medicine Show], 1981 (Box 14, Folder 258)
  - Outline: Medicine Show Book: clipping, outline drafts., undated (Box 14, Folder 259)
  - Medicine Show Correspondence: Correspondence., undated (Box 14, Folder 260)
  - Medicine Show Correspondence: Correspondence., undated (Box 14, Folder 261)
  - Medicine Show [photos]: Photographs., undated (Box 14, Folder 262)
  - Medicine Show [wall labels], undated (Box 15, Folder 263)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233844
  - Medicine Show [photos]: Photographs., undated (Box 15, Folder 264)
  - [Medicine Show] Fred Bloodgood: Correspondence, photocopies, drafts., undated (Box 15, Folder 265)
  - Correspondence: Medicine Show Book, undated (Box 15, Folder 266)
  - Medicine Show [Photos / Duplicates], undated (Box 15, Folder 267)
  - Medieval Performance: Photocopies, outline., undated (Box 15, Folder 268)
  - Medieval / Renaissance: Articles, photocopies, student work, class syllabus., undated (Box 15, Folder 269)
  - Melodrama I: Photocopies, articles, BM drafts, bibliographies, course materials., undated (Box 15, Folder 270)
  - Melodrama II: Clippings, photocopies, bibliography, one-act play., undated (Box 15, Folder 271)
  - Melodrama III: Articles, photocopies, programs, photographs, postcards, course materials, bibliographies, BM drafts., undated (Box 15, Folder 272)
  - Melodrama III: Photographic copies., undated (Box 35, Folder 675)
  - Melodrama IV: Clippings, articles, programs, bibliographies, course materials, student work, BM drafts., undated (Box 15, Folder 273)
  - Melodrama V: Student work., undated (Box 15, Folder 274)
  - Melodrama: Introduction: Clippings, course materials., undated (Box 15, Folder 275)
  - Melodrama: Domestic: Photocopies, student work, notes., undated (Box 15, Folder 276)
  - Melodrama: Production: Photocopies, student work., undated (Box 15, Folder 277)
  - Melodrama: Acting: Photocopies., undated (Box 15, Folder 278)
  - Melodrama: Temperance: Student paper, play excerpt, temperance pledges., undated (Box 15, Folder 279)
  - Melodrama: Military, Nautical and Equestrian: BM notes., undated (Box 15, Folder 280)
  - Melodrama: Oliver Twist: Photocopies., undated (Box 15, Folder 281)
  - Melodrama: Frontier, Indian, Wild West, Medicine Show: Article., undated (Box 15, Folder 282)
  - Melodrama: Grand Guignol: Photocopies, articles., undated (Box 15, Folder 283)
  - Melodrama: Stock, Temperance, Tom Show: Programs, flyer, notes, photocopy of guide to Barnum's museum., undated (Box 15, Folder 284)
  - Military Theatre: Article, brochure, program., undated (Box 15, Folder 285)
  - Minstrelsy I: Clippings, photocopies, bibliographies, student work; list of minstrel material from the Museum of the City of New York., undated (Box 16, Folder 286)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233851
  - Minstrelsy II: Student work (1995). (Box 16, Folder 287)
  - Minstrelsy III [sp. 1994-5]: Photocopies, articles., undated (Box 16, Folder 288)
  - Minstrelsy III [sp. 1994-5]: Photocopies, articles, bibliographies, course materials., undated (Box 16, Folder 289)
  - Minstrelsy IV: Photocopies, articles, course materials., undated (Box 16, Folder 290)
  - Minstrelsy IV: Photocopies, articles, bibliography., undated (Box 16, Folder 291)
  - Minstrelsy IV: Photocopies., undated (Box 16, Folder 292)
  - Minstrelsy IV: Photocopies, articles, bibliography., undated (Box 16, Folder 293)
  - Minstrelsy IV: Clippings, photocopies, articles, bibliographies, student work., undated (Box 16, Folder 294)
  - Minstrelsy V [course]: Photocopies, course materials, student paper., undated (Box 16, Folder 295)
  - Minstrelsy VI: Clippings, photocopies, programs, bibliographies, BM notes., undated (Box 16, Folder 296)
  - Minstrelsy VII [papers]: Photocopies, articles, correspondence, student work; program of African Consolidated Theatres' "Minstrel Scandals: Southern Africa Tour 1970-1971"., undated (Box 16, Folder 297)
  - Minstrelsy VIII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, photographs, correspondence, student work., undated (Box 16, Folder 298)
  - Minstrelsy IX [from Hatch Billops Collection]: Photocopies., undated (Box 17, Folder 299)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233869
  - Minstrelsy IX [from Hatch Billops Collection]: Photocopies., undated (Box 17, Folder 300)
  - Minstrelsy IX: Photocopies, correspondence, course materials., undated (Box 17, Folder 301)
  - Minstrelsy: Photocopies, course materials, student work., undated (Box 17, Folder 302)
  - Minstrelsy: Student work., undated (Box 17, Folder 303)
  - Minstrelsy: Photocopies, student work., undated (Box 17, Folder 304)
  - Minstrelsy [book]: Correspondence, programs for "The Merry Muldoons"., undated (Box 17, Folder 305)
  - Minstrelsy [misc.]: Photocopies, bibliographies., undated (Box 17, Folder 306)
  - Minstrelsy [xeroxes]: Photocopies, student work., undated (Box 17, Folder 307)
  - Minstrelsy [xeroxes]: Photocopies., undated (Box 17, Folder 308)
  - Mummings I: Photocopies, bibliographies, course materials., undated (Box 18, Folder 309)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233877
  - Mumming II: Student work., 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 310)
  - Mumming III: Article; 1982-3 issues of Roomer, The Newsletter of the Traditional Drama Research Group., undated (Box 18, Folder 311)
  - Museums: Clipping, brochures; 1971 bulletin of the Philadelphia Old Town Historical Society., undated (Box 18, Folder 312)
  - Music I: Clippings, articles, bibliographies, programs, fliers, correspondence., undated (Box 18, Folder 313)
  - Music II: Clippings, articles, bibliographies, programs, fliers, correspondence, student work., undated (Box 18, Folder 314)
  - Music Hall: Photocopies, articles; draft on Music Hall and Cabaret., undated (Box 18, Folder 315)
  - [Music Halls to Movie Palaces (exhibition)]: Exhibition information, catalog., undated (Box 18, Folder 316)
  - Music Programs I: Programs., undated (Box 18, Folder 317)
  - Musical Programs II: Programs., undated (Box 18, Folder 318)
  - Musical Theatre Papers I: Student work., undated (Box 18, Folder 319)
  - Musical Theatre II: Clippings, articles, bibliographies, programs, fliers, correspondence, student work., undated (Box 18, Folder 320)
  - Musical Theatre III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, student work; articles and publicity on Miles Kreuger and the Institute of the American Musical; 1921 issue of The World Magazine., undated (Box 18, Folder 321)
  - [Musical Theatre Archive], undated (Box 18, Folder 322)
  - [Musical Theatre in America Conference], undated (Box 18, Folder 323)